[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Ted Dansons character in Cheers?", "correct_answer": "Sam", "incorrect_answers": ["Dan", "Dom", "Joe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the main cause for Airline hull loss accidents from 1996 through 2005, according to a study by Boeing?", "correct_answer": "Flight crew error", "incorrect_answers": ["Bad weather", "Air traffic control", "Maintenance"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This rapper turned actor starred in 2 films with his children, 2006s The Pursuit of Happyness and 2008s I Am Legend.", "correct_answer": "Will Smith", "incorrect_answers": ["Ice Cube", "LL Cool J", "Ice T"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the popular movie and book murderer Sweeney Todd do with the bodies of his victims?", "correct_answer": "He makes them into meat pies.", "incorrect_answers": ["He burns them.", "He chops them into small pieces and buries them in different places.", "He feeds his dogs to them."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these lakes is deepest?", "correct_answer": "Tanganyika", "incorrect_answers": ["Caspian Sea", "Malawi or Nyasa", "Issyk-Kul"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If your pencil has a  reddish brown grain and a smell, what does that usually indicate?", "correct_answer": "It is made of  incense-cedar.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is made from non-incense-cedar.", "It is made from plastic.", "It is made of rainforest wood."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where does the female scorpion raise its young?", "correct_answer": "On her back", "incorrect_answers": ["In the roots of plants", "Under her abdomen", "In burrows in the ground"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following composers wrote the Moonlight Sonata  for piano?", "correct_answer": "Ludwig von Beethoven", "incorrect_answers": ["Claude DeBussey", "Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart", "Igor Stravinsky"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these are a part of an ant colony?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Drones", "Soldiers", "Workers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pink is the color of what ribbon?", "correct_answer": "Breast Cancer Awareness ribbon", "incorrect_answers": ["AIDS Awareness ribbon", "Ovarian Cancer Awareness ribbon", "Tuberculosis Awareness ribbon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the strongest opening bid in contract bridge according to Acol standards?", "correct_answer": "2 clubs", "incorrect_answers": ["2 No Trump", "3 diamonds", "2 spades"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many bones (on average) does the human body contain?", "correct_answer": "206", "incorrect_answers": ["207", "208", "205"]}]